扭曲的青春前期提要
Previously on Twisted...
- 这出车祸了 是Vikram - 有人移动了尸体
- There's been a car accident. It's Vikram. - Somebody must've moved the body.
- Jack. - 他为什么这么做?
- Jack. - Why would he do that for me?
他是为了我
He would do it for me.
当你向Vikram辞职时 你袭击了...
When you quit working for Vikram, you attacked...
你觉得我是那种人吗?
How could you think I'm capable of something like this?
你移动了他的尸体!
Well, you're capable of moving his body!
当我来到Green Grove 我是刚被少管所释放了
When I came to Green Grove, I was coming from juvie.
- 你认识Danny吗? - 我可能比你更了解他
- Did you know Danny? - I may know him better than you do.
我没有预谋杀死我父亲
I did not plan to kill my father.
你杀了你爸爸?
You killed your dad?
我还生过一个孩子 我想你可能知道
I had another baby. I thought you should know.
我知道 Vikram告诉过我
I did know. Vikram told me.
我知道他把收养协议放哪了
I know where he kept the adoption papers.
- 你想找你的孩子吗? - 当然想
- Do you want to find your child? - Of course I do.
- 男人们 他们... - 讨厌?
- Guys, they... - Suck?
还有说谎!
And lie!
- 出什么事了吗? - 可以这么说
- Something wrong? - You could say that.
- 你为什么抓他? - Lacey 你能先带她回家吗?
- Why did you arrest him? - Lacey, can you take her home?
你不告诉我他犯了什么罪 我就不走了
I'm not leaving until you tell me what he did.
- 我知道你想对Jo做什么 - 别打扰我和Jo
- And I know what you're doing with Jo. - Leave me and Jo the hell alone.
我来Green Grove是因为Danny把这说的不错
I came to Green Grove because Danny made it sound great.
他们在Danny爸爸的车里找到了我爸的DNA
They found my Dad's DNA in Danny's dad's car.
他们觉得我爸杀了他
They think that my Dad killed him.
听着 我肯定这只是个大误会
Look, I'm sure it's just a big misunderstanding.
我不知道 我是说 有DNA证据
I don't know. I mean, it's DNA.
- 是啊 但是... - 我知道我爸真的很爱Karen
- Sure, but... - And I know my Dad really loves Karen.
他一直很爱她 是他们的婚外情导致我父母离婚的
He always has. Their affair is what broke up my parents' marriage.
- 哦 我不... 我不... - 我搞不懂了
- Oh, I didn't... I didn't... - So I don't know,
或许他想 他的机会终于
maybe he thought... that was his chance
- 来了... - Whitney 你爸不是凶手
- to finally... - Whitney, your dad is not a killer.
我就是这么想的 你不了解他 你只是见过他
That's what I thought. You don't know him. You just met him.
好吧 你说得对 我 我或许不了解你爸
Okay, you're right, I... I may not know your dad,
但我非常肯定他没有杀Vikram
but I do know for sure that he did not kill Vikram.
- 你怎么知道? - 我就是知道 好吗?
- How do you know? - I just do, okay?
- 你认识Vikram Desai吗? - 认识
- Do you know Vikram Desai? - Yes.
你和他的妻子是不是有婚外情?
Have you been sleeping with his wife?
- 是的 - 喔 喔 喔 等等 等等
- Yes. - Whoa whoa whoa. Hold on, hold on.
抱歉 Taylor先生 但我必须要提醒你 你回答的这些
I'm sorry, Mr. Taylor, but I have to remind you that you're answering these
- 问题违背了法律顾问... - 我没什么好隐瞒了
- questions against the legal counsel... - I have nothing to hide.
我会回答他的任何问题
I'll answer anything he wants.
很好 那这个呢? 你是不是对Vikram的车做了手脚?
Good. How about this? Did you tamper with Vikram's car?
什么? 没有
What? No.
是你杀了他吗? 并假造了车祸现场?
Did you kill him? Make it look like an accident?
太荒谬了 下一个问题
That's absurd. Next question.
你做过Vikram的车吗?
Have you ever been inside Vikram's car?
很多年前 我是他的手下
I worked for him... Years ago.
但他死时开的那车 没有 从没坐过
But the car that he was driving when he died? No, never.
那为什么到处都是你的DNA呢?
Then why is your DNA all over it?
- 这不可能 这... - 这不仅可能 这是事实
- That's impossible. It... - It's not only possible, it's true.
- 你认为... - 我认为你杀了他
- So you think... - I think you killed him,
为了他的钱 为了能和他的妻子在一起
murdered him for the money... and a chance to be with his wife.
- 你怎么看呢? - 我现在还是保持沉默吧
- What do you think? - I think I'm gonna stop talking now.
Whitney 天呐
Whitney, my god.
听着 他们说你爸爸的事 都不是真的
Listen, what they're saying about your father, it's not true.
- 那不可能 - 是啊 我老听人这么说
- It's impossible. - Yeah, that's what I keep hearing.
- 额 我想见Jack - 抱歉 警长正在审问他
- Uh, I want to see Jack. - Sorry, the chief's in with him now.
当他结束审问后 他想跟你聊聊
And when he's done, he wants to talk to you.
Danny 你先把Lacey和Whitney送回家 好吗?
Danny, why don't you take Lacey and Whitney home, okay?
-我觉得我不 - 你和我们一起住
- I don't think I... - You're staying with us.
- 我保证会没事的 - 不 我是说我不能丢下我爸爸
- I'll make sure it's okay. - No, I mean I'm not leaving my Dad.
宝贝 我经历过这些
Honey, I've been through this.
他们短期内不会让你见他的
They're not gonna let you see him anytime soon.
这是事实 现在除了去休息一会
It's true. There's nothing else you can do right now
其他的事你无能为力
except for try to get some rest.
是啊 想得真美
Yeah, like that's gonna happen.
你知道吗 Whitney Danny说的对 我们或许该走了
You know, Whitney, Danny's right. We should probably go.
好吧 我不管了
Okay, whatever.
我告诉你 我们会搞清楚这事的 好吗?
I'm telling you, we're gonna figure this out, okay?
是啊 这是最好了
Yeah, we'd better.
- 谢谢让我和你们住在一起 - 应该的 不客气
- Thank you for letting me stay with you. - Uh, of course, no worries.
我想去洗个澡 或许能借我个运动衫吗?
I just gotta take a shower. Maybe I can borrow some sweats?
- 当然 都在楼上 - 谢谢
- Sure, yeah, it's all upstairs. - Thank you.
嗨 Whitney 我想我先走了
Oh, hey, Whitney, I think I'm gonna take off
- 如果你没意见 - 哦 好啊
- if you're okay. - Oh, yeah.
我想我妈可能会担心了 这么晚了
I'm just my Mom's probably worried. It's so late.
- 当然 抱歉 - 不 请别说抱歉了
- Of course, I'm sorry. - No, please. "Sorry"?
Lacey 你真好 非常感谢你
Lacey, you're been... amazing. Thank you so much.
- 我早上给你打电话 好吗? - 好
- I'll call you in the morning, okay? - Great.
过来
Come here.
听着 我什么都没说 因为
Look, I didn't say anything, because...
- 我不知道 或许我该说的 - Lacey 不 听着
- Well, I don't know. Maybe I should have. - Lacey, no, look...
你得做些什么 你不能让的Whitney爸爸为你背黑锅
You need to do something. You can't let Whitney's dad take the blame for this.
我明白 好吗? 没人比我更清楚这感受
I know, okay? No one understands that better than I do.
我让我妈妈请了纽约最好的律师
I got my Mom to call the best lawyer in New York.
她在来的路上了... 别担心了
She's on her way now... so just don't worry.
很晚了 我应该走了
It's late. I should get out of here.
天呐 难以置信我睡着了
Oh my god, I can't believe I fell asleep.
这太尴尬了
This is so embarrassing.
不 没什么的
No, it's so not.
我庆幸你会舒服的睡着
I'm glad you felt comfortable enough to sleep.
很明显 我也睡了
Clearly so did I.
- 妈妈 - 嘿 Masterson夫人
- Mom. - Hey, Ms. Masterson.
什么都没发生 我们只是
Nothing happened. We were just...
你爸在哪呢? 他还没回来吗?
Where's your father? Isn't he home yet?
我们不会... 额 因为...
We wouldn't be... well, because of...
- 我不知道他在哪 - 几小时前我和他谈过
- I don't know where he is. - I spoke to him hours ago.
我以为他现在该在家 这是疯狂的一夜
I thought he'd be home by now. It's been a crazy night.
- 为什么? 发生了什么事? - Jack Taylor因杀害Vikram被抓了
- Why? What happened? - Jack Taylor was arrested for killing Vikram,
我得去打电话给你爸爸
so I need to go call your dad.
- Jack... Jack Taylor? 那不是... - 是啊 你该走了
- Jack... Jack Taylor? Isn't that... - Yeah, you should go.
不 我能留下 让我帮你吧
No, I can stay. Let me help you.
拜托 我只是... 我需要去和Danny谈谈
Please, I just... I just need to talk to Danny.
好吧
All right.
Jack没事吧? 他承认任何事了吗?
Is Jack all right? Did he admit to anything?
你明白我不能跟你讨论这些的
You know I can't talk about that with you.
好吧 那 我先回家了
All right, well, I'm gonna go home and then...
事实上 如果你不介意 我还有些问题想问你 请进
Actually, I have a couple of questions to ask you if you don't mind. Please.
- Kyle. - 请坐
- Kyle. - Have a seat.
我知道你们俩有婚外情
I know you two were having an affair.
严格来说 那不是婚外情 我丈夫死了
Technically, it's not an affair. My husband's dead.
但这事是在他死前开始的 对吗?
But it started before he died, right?
多年前 Jack和我是在一起过
Jack and I were together years ago,
- 但结束了 - 为什么?
- but it ended. - Why?
因为他明白了你永远不会离开Vikram吗
'Cause he realized you were never gonna leave Vikram?
- 你在审讯我吗? - 只是问些问题
- Are you interrogating me? - Just asking some questions.
- 如果你需要叫律师来 - 不 不需要
- If you need to call a lawyer... - No, I'm fine.
你告诉过Jack人身意外保险的事吗?
Did you ever tell Jack about that life insurance policy?
一千万美元?
$10 million?
说过 但是在他们找到Vikram尸体的那晚
Yes, but not until the night they found Vikram's body.
Jack整晚都和我在一起 所以...
And Jack was with me the whole night, so...
死亡时间大约是四十八小时前
The time of death was about 48 hours earlier.
那车在溪谷里有段时间了
The car had been in that gully for a while.
那地方还很偏僻
It's a pretty remote spot.
但Jack不知道钱的事
But Jack didn't know about the money then.
他曾经为Vikram工作过 对吗?
He used to work for Vikram, right?
我是说 或许Vikram告诉过他保险的事
I mean, maybe Vikram told him about the policy
或者他自己发现了什么 你觉得呢?
or he found out some other way, don't you think?
我猜这 有可能把
I guess it's... possible.
你觉得Jack有能力杀人吗?
Do you think Jack is capable of murder?
Karen 你有任何Jack希望Vikram死的理由吗?
Karen, do you have any reason to believe that Jack wanted Vikram dead?
我觉得没有 但 我不知道
I didn't think so, but... I don't know.
我不知道
I just don't know.
这个律师怎么样? 因为我不会让
How good is this lawyer? 'cause I'm not letting
一个无辜的人因为我做的事而进监狱的
an innocent man go to jail for something that I did.
他也不是那么无辜
Well, he's not exactly innocent.
他是那个伪造车祸现场的人
He's the one who staged the accident.
- 为了我 为了我们 - 或许吧
- As a favor to me, to us. - Well, maybe.
或许Jack在我提到人身意外保险之前
Maybe Jack knew about the life insurance policy
就知道这件事的
before I even mentioned it.
或许他希望他们找到你爸爸的尸体
Maybe he wanted them to find your dad's body
那我们就可以申请赔款了
so that we could claim the money.
等等 你在说什么啊?
Wait, what are you talking about?
- 你说过他是个好人 - 我知道
- You're the one who said he was this nice guy... - I know.
Vikram告诉过Tess他有生命危险
Vikram told Tess that his life was in danger,
在Jack去找他之后他就失踪了
and he disappeared after Jack went to see him.
- 他们打了一架 所以 - 所以什么 你觉得Jack
- They had a big fight, so... - So what, you think Jack
六个月前就试图杀了他吗?
tried to kill him six months ago?
我是说 那又怎么样呢?
I mean, what does that matter now?
我只是说或许Jack也不是什么圣人
I'm just saying maybe Jack isn't such a saint after all.
不管他做了什么 不管他什么动机
Whatever he did, whatever his motives,
我是那个杀死我爸爸的人
I'm the one who killed my Dad.
而现在 这才是最重要的
And right now, that is all that matters.
天呐 你来这做什么?
Oh my god, what are you doing here?
我要跟Danny谈谈
I need to talk to Danny.
- 好吧 但 - 没事的
- Fine, but... - It's okay.
交给我吧 谢谢
I got it. Thanks.
- 过来 - Danny. Danny
- Come on. - Danny. Danny.
听着 不管Jack会向我爸交代所有事 或
Look, either Jack's about to tell my Dad everything or...
不 如果他想说什么 他早就说了
No, if he was gonna say anything, he would've done it by now.
所以他为了你背黑锅?
So he's just gonna cover for you?
他会为了他没做过的事而进监狱吗
He's gonna go to prison for a murder he didn't commit?
你不能让他这么做 Danny
You can't let him do that, Danny.